thecricketlounge.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy - The Cricket Lounge

### Online Privacy Policy

Thecricketlounge.com is strongly dedicated to your to privacy and also to keeping the private information secure. To earn your trust within our commitment, we’re fully revealing our privacy practices. We encourage you to definitely read our privacy statement to understand kinds of your personal data we collect and just how we make use of this information. Thecricketlounge has the authority to amend its online privacy policy to match the requirements of the web site and we’ll let you know concerning the up-to-date rules at the earliest possible time.

**The way we collect and employ information**

Thecricketlounge only collects the required your personal data to be able to react to your demands for the personalized items and services. Your personal data includes, however, is not restricted to, first and surname, street address, e-mail address, telephone number, interests, date of birth, and then any additional information that itself identifies or when associated with the above mentioned information, may identify you like a specific individual.This site doesn’t collect your personal data in regards to you except whenever you particularly and knowingly provide it. Thecricketlounge uses your personal data to function the website and services and tell you of recent features, services, and items from thecricketlounge.com.

**User/member interaction features**

thecricketlounge.com has numerous features that offer for customers/people to reveal their details and contact other customers/people. Your utilization of such features and disclosure associated with a personal particulars (e.g. e-mail address) on your part with these features are in your sole risk and thecricketlounge.com accepts no responsibility for the similar. However, in case your privacy continues to be intruded consequently of taking part such features, you can inform us by e-mail at editor@thecricketlounge.com.

**Other Websites**

thecricketlounge.com site consists of links with other websites. thecricketlounge.com is not accountable for the privacy practices or even the content of these websites.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [//www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

The Cricket Lounge has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Inform Us**

If you think that any article, picture or video on Thecricketlounge.com is objectionable or illegal, you can report by sending an email at editor@thecricketlounge.com or thecricketlounge2013@gmail.com. We assure you that, if it is found ojectionable or illegal, a prompt action will be taken against the reported article, picture or video.
